dbeaver.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy policy – DBeaver

We believe that the personal information you provide to us must be both kept private, and used in a responsible fashion. Therefore, we consistently put our best efforts towards achieving both these objectives. 

###### Types and Reasons for Data Collection

When you register to download a product some personal information is required. This information is used to identify a user as the license owner. 

###### Web Site Traffic and Analysis

DBeaver Corp gathers and analyzes information about our users’ routine use of the web site. We use this information to monitor what areas of the site are most popular, and adjust the focus of our continuous development efforts. 

###### Access to Information Collected

As a registered user of DBeaver Corp you can simply and easily update your information at any time – just enter appropriate updates in your profile at the web site. 

###### User Preferences, Opt Out

If at any time you wish to be removed from our database, simply send an email with the subject “remove” to [support@dbeaver.com](mailto:support@dbeaver.com) and we will promptly cancel your records. DBeaver requires that users provide information requested in the registration screens for reasons specified in the user registration agreement. This information is essential to us properly organize our service. As more functionality is added to the site, we will continue to develop mechanisms and policies that best address participants’ preferences related to information collection and use. 

###### Use of Web Browser ‘Cookies’

Cookies are used at the DBeaver web site for maintaining sessions only. Sensitive information, such as telephone numbers, passwords, and credit card numbers are never stored in cookies. 

###### Security

DBeaver Corp is concerned about the security of the personal data that we collect and put in place measures to prevent unauthorized access to that information. 

###### Updates to the Privacy Policy

DBeaver is sensitive to user’s privacy issues and recognizes the need to update this policy as new features and business services are offered. Any changes of the privacy policy are announced at the DBeaver web site. If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us.
